*小影 襞葑g作*
*Tf：三次出生入死伊拉克 始K未@o急Y助*
*德州米德my行*
安oc
Quiet.
把T打_ 快_T
Open the door,
open the door.
致
What?
@到底怎N回事
What in the devil?
女士你站起 收y抽显谀难Y?
Can you please stand up
and take us to the cash drawer, ma'am?
想都e想 - e敬酒不吃
- I will not.
- We ain't asking.
抽犀F在]有F金
There's no money
in the drawers yet.
X都在保U箱Y 我又不知道密a
It's in the safe
and I ain't got the code.
C明一下
Prove it.
打_抽!
Drawer!
打_
Here.
打_抽
Open the drawer.
匙o我啊 - 匙
- I need the keys.
- Keys.
往後站
Step back.
操他的
Shit. Damn it!
你是新人? 我猜的
Y'all are new at this,
I'm guessing.
X在哪? - f了在保U
- Where's the money?
- I told you, it's in the safe.
那l才知道密a? - 克谏先生
- Well, who has the code?
- Mr. Clauson.
他R上到 我建h你so收手
He'll be here soon
and I suggest you fellers don't be.
你@N小嚎谱镄姓媸翘傻了
All you're guilty of right now
is being stupid.
so走 @事也就算了
Just leave and that's all it'll be.
你再f一遍我傻看
Tell me I'm stupid again.
克谏什Nr候^? - 你看著我
What time does Mr. Clauson get here?
Ma'am, look at me.
克谏什Nr候^?
What time does
Mr. Clauson get here, huh?
每天上午8c30分
8:30 every morning.
快走
We're walking.
坐下
And sit.
你要去哪?地板上坐好了!
Where do you think you're going?
Sit on the floor!
你才傻呢
You're stupid.
eo我多事 H鄣
This ain't about you, darling.
埃希 你好?
Elsie, you all right?
早上好
Good morning.
你不用非得揍他的
You didn't have to hit him.
慢c_ - 就@速度了
- Slow down.
- I ain't speeding.
看] 老弟 不用杞人n天
See, little brother,
not a worry in the world.
]有化快
Planning this and doing it
is two different things.
dS我先去W尼
Maybe we should get there ahead,
get up to Olney.
早起的B翰庞邢x吃嘛
Early bird gets the worm.
慢c - 就@速度了
- Slow down.
- I ain't speeding.
我在Y}找到@些硬
I found these coins
in the barn.
鬼知道它在那Y多久了
Lord knows how long
they've been sitting there.
我每天衣s食 才了@些硬
I've been living off an inmate's diet,
and had all these coins
一直在料袋子底下埋著
sitting right underneath
a bunch of feed sacks.
@上面印著1953 - 1953?
- This one says 1953.
-1953?
f不定有收藏r值
I wonder if any of these
is collector's items.
那你可就坐硪蛔金山了
You could be sitting
on a fortune here.
希望吧
I hope so.
夥早上好 打_抽
Good morning, folks.
Open the drawer!
快他把抽洗蜷_
Open the motherfucking drawer!
只要1、5、10、20K 不要一百的 不要成捆的
Ones, fives, 10s, 20s,
no hundreds, no bundles.
你y行呢? - ]嘴
- You boys robbing the bank?
- Shut up.
手放上 快放在上
Put your hands on the counter.
On the counter.
是 先生 - @就α 快c
- Yes, sir.
- That's it, come on.
真了 你比墨西哥人不如
That's crazy.
Y'all ain't even Mexicans.
不要成捆的
Uh-uh, uh-uh.
No bundles.
就要散X
Just loose cash.
好的
Okay-
你可不害臊
You ought to be
ashamed of yourselves.
手放上 放我能看的地方
Hands on the counter
where I can see them!
是 先生
Yes, sir.
老子身上有]?
You got a gun on you, old man?
老子身上就是有 咋地
You're damn right
I got a gun on me.
快拿下他的啊 - 知道了
- Are you gonna get his gun?
- Yeah.
控住鲎有胁恍?
Keep up with
the circumstances, okay?
拿到了 - 你打算我的?
- Yeah, I got it.
- So are y'all gonna steal my gun, too?
我自然了
I have my own gun.
我不是你的 我只y行
We ain't stealing from you.
We're stealing from the bank.
感激不M
Much obliged.
撤走!
Let's go!
不好意思啦
Sorry about this, folks.
z臭不要的王八僮
Dirty, rotten sons of bitches.
操你的老^子!
Fuck you, old man!
快走 跑啊!
Go, run, go!
你他把放在上?想害死我?
Put the gun on the counter?
You trying to get us killed?
我不老人家的|西
I ain't stealing
from some old man.
一次只玩一票 H此
We're stealing
from one place, that's it.
你就要成可z巴巴的小罪犯了
You're turning out to be
a poor-ass criminal.
L僮
Oh, fuck you.
Whoo!
早起的小B真的有x吃吧?
See what the early bird gets?
]饰可以去茴D分行忠黄?
Maybe we should hit
that branch in Jayton?
不能 我只鹊你y行
No, we ain't.
We hit those banks
早上第一票真他蠢 空的
first thing in the fucking morning,
when they're empty.
在]人的r候去 - 真他的
- When they're empty, God damn it!
- All right.
@是我最後一次被人射
It's the last time
I care to be shot at.
我得放明c 老干半吊子的事情
We got to be smart.
We're a ways from being finished.
我他可以@N^一周
Shit, I can do this all week.
等著瞧
We're gonna.
老弟啊 我好比科曼奇人
We're like the Comanches,
little brother,
S心所欲搞突u
raiding wherever we please
整德州都抓不住我一根毛
with the whole of Texas
hunting our shadow.
平原之王
Lord of the Plains.
手拿下去 - L你蛋
- Hands off.
- Fuck off!
f那些y行的了?
You hear about these bank robberies?
你槭颤N跟我撞衫?
Why are you always
dressed like me?
@是我的制服
This is our uniform.
我]什N制服
We ain't got no uniform.
你可以x自己喜g色的r衫穿
You can wear whatever
color shirt you choose.
你一直W我而已
You just keep choosing mine.
巡警手著可以穿白色、{色或者棕色的r衫
Ranger regs say white,
blue, or tan dress shirts.
基於t 我可以穿同拥囊r衫
Stands to reason every once in a while
we're gonna be dressed the same.
你很明白什N叫做跟屁x 阿托
Well, you know what they say
about imitation, Alberto.
你到底想摸摸@些y行匪的老底
You wanna hear
about these bank robberies,
是就在@坐著 那些蠢蛋逍b法外?
or you'll just sit there
and let Alzheimer's run its course?
他都去^哪?
Where are they at?
德州米德my行...
Texas Midlands--
阿爻欠中 和W尼分行
the branch in Archer City
and the branch in Olney.
FBI有]有通令?
FBI want an assist?
米德my行在德州以外 ]有分支C
Midlands ain't got
any branches outside Texas.
何r他也只是浊K
Plus, they're just hitting the drawers
for a few thousand.
FBI才械霉苣
FBI don't want it.
你]蔬能找c纷...
You may get to have some fun
趁你]退休
before they send you off
to the rocking chair yet.
o我清醒c
I need you sober.
l他喝瓶啤酒就醉了?
Who the hell gets drunk
off a beer?
@破地方真透了
Place looks like shit.
你有什N想f的?
You got anything else
you wanna say?
@地方BK像拥呐Ｅ哦]有
There's not a decent steak
@群]用的|西
in the whole lot
of them sorry sons of bitches.
是啊 你光著蹲子的r候
Yeah, well,
while you were busy in jail,
我忙著照咱老
I was busy looking after Mama,
所以你管去死吧
so you can go fuck yourself.
她在那睡床瘟硕嗑?
Was she in that bed awhile?
三月
Three months.
最後A段 人走得也很辛苦
The end there was pretty rough.
要是她跟我_口 我也能退的
I could've helped out a little
if she asked.
我至少也能喂j那些瘦巴巴的牛
I could've fed
them skinny cows.
我]|西jo它
We had nothing to feed them.
那我也能打咭幌路块g啊
Well, I could've helped clean up
the house a bit.
]把你成是房g打叩慕KY者
Never took you for the go-to guy
for house cleaning.
不 我只是y行的而已
No. Just robbing banks.
是啊
You know.
去她的
Fuck her.
她才不想跟我有什N瓜葛
She never wanted nothing
to do with me anyway.
她留z诹?
She leave a will?
留了
Yeah.
包括我?
Am I in it?
z]什N好看
The will don't matter.
她把所有的|西都留o了我 星期五生效w我鹤
She left everything to me.
By Friday it all goes to my boys.
她@N做]e的意思
She didn't mean nothing by it.
她^故意的
She damn sure meant it.
她一直很恨我c老爹χ干
She always hated me
for standing up to him.
我都得到了土P
We all got punished.
你不懂 χ干造成的痛更持久
You never understood that fighting back
makes the beating last longer.
不 我懂
No, I understood.
所以我]再打架 直接懒四狗娘B的
That's why I stopped fighting
and shot that son of a bitch.
嘿 怎N回事?
Hey, What's going on?
有人今早了y行
Somebody robbed
the bank this morning.
至耸颤N?
Do what?
如果你看可疑人物...
If you see anyone
looking a little sideways,
give me a call.
可疑人物可不想碰我
Sideways don't wanna meet me.
碰我 就是他找K子上吊的r候
Find itself on the wrong end
of a short rope.
那真是辛苦你 pp了其他人不少工作
Oh, well, that would simplify things
for everyone but you.
也S吧 要上吊先得找涫遣皇
Maybe,
if you can find the tree.
天 我畚鞯轮
God, I love West Texas.
巡警好 - 你好 (德州警察被Q檠簿)
- Ranger.
- Hi there.
劫殿~不多
Wasn't much of a robbery.
只了不到7000美元
Got off with just under $7,000.
了里的X 只面值低於20元的X 是散X
Took the drawer money,
20s and under, only loose bills.
]防I染料? - ]有
- No ink pack?
- Nope.
明 - 明的作案手法
- Smart.
- That was smart.
我能看一下O控像?
Can we get a look
at the video?
我o你介By行理吧 克谏先生
Let me introduce you
to the bank manager, Mr. Clauson.
@位是巡警h密D
This here is Ranger Hamilton.
巡警好 - 你好
- Ranger.
- Sir.
我可以看下O控像?
Can we get a look
at the surveillance video?
我以前有z像^的 最近搞O控底只...
We got cameras, but they're
switching us over to a digital system
以便B接到X系y
that feeds into the computer.
新b的z像^K]有B接到我自己的像O
These new cameras
don't hook to our VCRs.
把你Y的小警L叫
Call over
the Young County Sheriffs.
他有]有把z像^接到...
Ask them if they thought
to hook their cameras
任何O渖
to some sort of
recording device.
有武器? - 有 手
- Armed?
- Yes, sir. Pistols.
哦
Oh.
遮住了?
Faces covered?
滑雪面具 \由 的子...
Ski masks, sweatshirts,
baggy pants...
好的 - 就像_拉斯的暴徒
- Uh-huh.
- Like them thugs in Dallas.
吸毒的 也S?
Tweakers, maybe?
可能吧
Maybe.
今天早上有吸毒犯作案
A little early in the morning
for tweakers.
吸毒犯不睡X的 只犯毒a
Tweakers don't sleep.
They just tweak.
他只店、泊 不y行
They rob drug stores
and parked cars, not banks.
我能M去看看?
Can I take a look inside?
好的 L官
Yes, sir.
是 我到了 格利特
Yeah, I'm here, Margaret.
他打了你的鼻子 ?
So they bopped you
in the snozzola, huh?
是的
Yes, sir.
算好的了
Not very nice.
我知道他的遮住了 但你能分辨出N族?
I know their faces was covered,
but could you tell their race?
黑人是白人?
Black, white?
你f的是他的w色是他的心?
Their skin or their souls?
我先不他是否黑心
Let's leave their souls
out of this for now.
白人
White.
我猜他就住在附近
From around here somewhere
is my guess,
姆直嫠的口音砜
you know, from their voices.
是?
Oh?
P郡l生同影缸 在W尼分行
Young County says same deal
with the branch in Olney.
稍等一下
Excuse me.
他有像?
Do they have video?
]有像 c本行似
Same deal all the way around.
沃不是有u各N子a品的?
Doesn't Walmart sell all sorts
of electronic equipment?
e老是我f的
My word.
Get your hands off that.
那些砘r不收手 相信我
Well, these boys, they aren't done yet,
I'll tell you that.
怎N解? - 他很有耐心
- How come?
- Well, they're patient.
猿种荒贸涎Y的X 牟荒谜百的X
They're just sticking to the drawers,
not taking the hundreds.
百元n票是y行的X 能被跟
That's the bank's money.
We can trace that.
他想一大PX
They're trying to raise
a certain amount.
@是我的猜想
That's my guess.
他要一些X才能蚰枪PX
It's gonna take
a few banks to get there.
你鹤知道他就要l了?
Your boys know how rich
they're gonna be?
他什N都不知道呢
They don't know anything yet.
你他去⒓釉岫Y了?
You take them to the funeral?
我f了 他什N都不知道
Like I said,
they don't know anything.
你上回他是什Nr候?
When's the last time
you saw them?
我一起斯坦福去看了技表演 你正好出z
When we all went to the rodeo
in Stamford right after you got out.
那就是一年前了 - 我F在跟他用M
- That was a year ago.
- I talk to them on the phone.
你跟他M?
You talk to them on the phone?
想我的建h? - 不想
- You want a little advice?
- No. No, I don't.
明天去看看他
Go see them tomorrow.
你知道我欠了黛比多少子女狃BM?
You got any idea how much
I owe Debbie in child support?
你F在兜Y有足虻腻X
You've got enough in your front pocket
to fix that problem right now.
@X不能 你很清楚
We can't spare it,
you know that.
也S我再忠黄狈中
Maybe we should hit
another branch.
知道 你f的好像我[不了@行似的
You know, you talk like
we ain't gonna get away with this.
我就]到^有人可以至诉@行全身而退的
I've never met nobody who got away
with anything, ever.
{你?
You?
那你他槭颤N同意诌@行?
Then why in the hell
did you agree to do it?
因槭悄阋求的 兄弟
Because you asked,
little brother.
我去拉屎 老了不中用
I got to shit like an old goat.
你去I 在前T等我
Grab the check,
meet me out front.
我f的 算是暗示吧
Well, if that isn't a hint,
I don't know what is.
喜g@牛排? - 是的 女士
- You like your steak?
- Yes, ma'am.
你有很L一段路程要走啊
Well, you've got
a ways to go yet.
是啊 非要等我吃完 你得等一天
Yeah, you'll be waiting around all day
for me to finish this.
o你吃不吃完 我都在@Y上班 所以...
I'll be here whether
you finish it or not, so...
你慢用
you take your time.
e出
Sure is quiet in here.
打_X 5、10、20K的都o我拿出
Open the drawer.
Fives, 10s, 20s.
把X整理好[到桌子上
Fan them out
like a deck of cards.
你是做什N的?
What do you do?
上一份工作是在...
Last job was for a...
天然夤司
natural gas company.
起硇剿不e
Sounds high-dollar.
不 井可]那N高的工Y
No, there ain't nothing
high-dollar about drilling.
F在好像]人天然饩了
No one seems to be
drilling for gas now, anyway.
都是石油井
They're sure drilling for oil.
我是f l知道下一有什Na出?
I mean, ain't one drill
the same as the next?
我也@N想
That's my take on it.
我X得我得e人相信我的...
Guess I got to get
someone else to believe me.
婊子B的
Son of a bitch!
我需要一N
We could use a cook.
小建h而已
Just a thought.
上菜了 詹妮・安
Order's up, Jenny Ann.
再
Bye.
快l!
Start the car!
操
Shit!
操 死
Fuck! Shit!
快走 快 快!
Go, go, go!
我敢打你的子女扶BM^Σ灰@多
I bet you don't owe this much
in child support.
我一定了才找你兔
I must be out of my goddamn mind
to ask you for help.
你想要害死我?!
You wanna get us killed?!
Huh?!
@不是米德m的分行 不在
That's not a Midlands Branch.
That's not part of the plan.
F在我得回去牧雎褴 - 操
Now, we got to go back to the ranch
and bury the car.
操! - 不 不需要那N做
- Fuck!
- No, we do not.
我距x俄克拉荷R州只有不到一半路程了
We're over halfway to Oklahoma.
我不要_一v偷淼能去印第安
I'm not driving a stolen getaway car
to a fucking Indian casino.
你拖累我要晚一天
You just put us
a goddamn day behind.
但@票干的不e 所以F在我扯平了
Well, I got us a day ahead
this morning, so I guess we're even.
不用x我 - x你大
- You're welcome.
- Fuck you.
你不能自己接?
Can't you answer
your own phone?
我在_ 而你只是坐在那Y掰手指
I'm driving. You're just sitting there
twiddling your fat fingers.
非巡警h密D本人
Ranger Hamilton's phone.
真是太大妄
It's reckless is what it is.
是吸毒犯 相信我
It's tweakers, I'm telling you.
我不X得他有那N莽
I don't think these boys
is reckless.
^Σ皇俏毒犯
Damn sure ain't tweakers.
他十分清楚自己在做什N
They know exactly
what they're doing.
你是不是一定要@得比e人明 才能活下去?
I don't know how you're gonna survive
without somebody to outsmart.
你得有酆 易W的那N
You need a hobby, and quick.
TR怎N?
How about a horse?
・z是TR的
Mary Beth was the rider.
R只我想起她
A horse would only
remind me of her.
喜g~?
You like to fish.
不至於每天都~吧
Not enough to do it
every goddamn day.
等我退休
Yeah, when I retire,
我要和埃斯米搬到加S斯敦
I'm gonna move Esme and me
down to Galveston.
I一lO船
Buy a fishing boat.
住在a^旁 靠他打O生活
Gonna live on that son of a bitch
right at the pier.
哦 l知道呢?
Oh, who knows?
f不定那些劫犯
Maybe one of these bank robbers
is gonna want a gunfight
那我就可以戴著光s煺峦诵萘
and I can dodge my retirement
in a blaze of glory.
你的法我可R^
Well, I've seen you shoot.
和光s@勺职朦c都沾不上
There won't be much glory in it.
哦 至少我是挺幸\的
Oh, well, I'm lucky
上有替我蟪鸬幕煅
I got a half-breed by my side
to avenge me.
希望你保持清醒久一c
If you can stay sober
long enough,
知道你原住民有多俦中物
knowing how you lnjuns
like the bottle.
Whoa.
Hey!
你在致 放火地?
What you all doing?
You burning this field?
我吃了蔚?
Why in the shit
would we do that?
@火是公路那淼 追我很久了
This kicked up on the highway,
been chasing us ever since.
真希望我能蜕夏愕拿
Wish we could do
something for you.
是它把我成灰斫饷我吧
Ought to just let it turn me to ashes,
put me out of my misery.
剪了那h笆
Cut that fence.
都21世o了 我在s牲口c火谋荣著^河
21st century, I'm racing a fire
to the river with a herd of cattle.
算知道我家孩子槭颤N不想诌@行了
And I wonder why my kids
won't do this shit for a living.
走起 快走
Move 'em out.
Come on.
快 快 快
Go, go! go-
你要求支援?
You wanna call it in?
等它到布拉索斯河 自己就绲
Oh, it's gonna burn out
when it hits the Brazos.
再f@荒山野X的哪赫业玫绞颤N支援
No one to call
around here, anyway.
@些小子只能靠自己了
No, these boys is on their own.
我是不明白有什N} 托比
I still don't see the problem, Toby.
你是...
You still don't...
}在於 拜你所n
Well, the problem is,
thanks to you,
我必挨到明早 再去搞v
we have to spend tomorrow morning
getting another car,
所以L三得杉毅y行
so we'll have to hit two banks
on Wednesday.
我今天已了三家了
We already done three today.
e心了
Stop worrying.
@是l的地P?
Whose land is this?
苋鹈住炭
Jeremy Chalker.
他我待在@Y l件是退打土狼
He lets me stay here in exchange
for shooting coyotes.
冰箱Y有冰啤酒
Cold beer in the fridge.
你偷了我的帽子
You stole my hat.
是借
I borrowed it.
你他λ做了什N?
What the fuck you do to it?
@是什N? - 我的一家一
- What's this?
- My livelihood.
我用不著全上
We don't need all this.
不能天天把放在房上啊
Can't keep the guns
in the trailer days on end.
@然也不能нMy行
That's not coming with us
in the bank.
和出{T吧
Just spoke to the teller.
她有c牧
She's a little shook up.
可能她的{照被拿走了
Perp took her driver's license,
用以威{家人 使她]嘴
threatened her family
if she talked to us.
你叫什N名字 @位年p的女士?
Mind if I ask you
your name, young lady?
娜塔莉・R丁人
Natalie Martinez.
好的 娜塔莉 我希望你知道
Well, Natalie,
I want you to know
在我抓到@些歹徒之前...
we're gonna have some officers
watching your house extra careful
派警T守在你家附近
till we catch these buggers.
我向你保C
You have my word on that.
不止一歹徒?
There's more than one?
y行的只有一?
Only one man robbed the bank?
是的 - 他L什N?
- Yeah.
- What'd he look like?
他穿的像牛仔 但戴了滑雪面具
He was dressed like a cowpoke
except for the ski mask.
他好像逃M了停在餐^外面的Y
I think he ran to a car
that was parked out front of the diner.
你看到有?
You saw the car?
G色的
It was green.
壮尚碌幼? - 我不是很懂 先生
- How old?
- I don't know cars, mister.
好吧 那看起硎禽v好 是一般的
Well, was it a nice car,
an okay car,
或者是超破?
or a real piece of shit?
超破
It was a real piece of shit.
好的 F在我有c索了
All right.
Now, we're getting somewhere.
那砹艘有XI屋的男人
Oh, that looks like a man
who could foreclose on a house.
我先走一步了 {塔利
Excuse me, Natalie.
打_一下 行L先生
Excuse me, Mr. Banker.
{塔利 在你父H抵_前 我派警Tc你一起
Natalie, I'm gonna have the officer
stay with you till your father arrives.
好? - 好的
- All right?
- Okay.
你今早有]有碰巧到O控 有?
Didn't happen to have your surveillance
cameras on this morning, did you?
然
Of course.
所以你拍到@起劫了
Oh, so you have
the robbery on video.
@是然
Of course we do.
如果]有O控 我算是y行?
What kind of bank would we be
if we didn't have video surveillance?
@然德州米m德y行例外
Oh, you'd be
a Texas Midlands Bank.
好的 那我有像了
All right, we've got video.
我去街角h堡店t解下情r 拜仔看下像?
Care to give it a watch
while I wander over to the burger joint?
能臀翼便c吃的?
Would you order me something
while you're there?
我好I - 我岩伤家有]有乾肉u（北美印地安人的一N主要食品）
- I'm starving.
- I doubt they serve pemmican.
你知道我也算墨西哥人
You know
I'm part Mexican, too.
好吧 如果哪天我玩蛄擞〉诎踩说亩巫
Yeah, well,
I'm gonna get to that
我住玩墨西哥人的段子
when I'm through
with the Indian insults,
不^那是很久以後的事了
but it's gonna be a while.
你@些巡警都@N怪?
You rangers are an odd bunch.
不 他是例外
No, just him.
我看看像吧
Let's take a look at that video.
好 就在@後面
Yeah, it's right back here.
您好
Howdy.
女士
Ma'am.
我猜你知道y行l生的事吧
Guess you know about
the goings-on at the bank.
我]注意
I did notice.
今天有外地人磉^?
Any out-of-towners
come through today?
詹妮・安在@服者^男的 不是本地人
Jenny Ann waited on a couple of boys,
ain't from here.
哦?
Oh?
我去叫她
I'll go get her.
非常感x
Appreciate that.
朋友
Boys.
你在@坐了挺久了吧?
Y'all been here for a while?
挺久了 久到目袅四...
Well, long enough to watch
a bank getting robbed
我30年X的y行被的全^程
that's been robbing me
for 30 years.
所以你看他了?
Oh, you say you've seen them?
我可以十分_定f 他是坐在那吃的午
I'm pretty sure they were sitting
right over there having lunch.
其中一高
One of them was tall.
另一矮
The other one was short.
都和牛仔一邮
They's both lean like cowboys.
要我f的 看起硐袷切值
Looked like brothers
if you ask me.
你是德州巡警?
You the Texas Ranger?
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
和我你服盏哪年p英俊的陌生人吧
Tell me about those handsome
young strangers that you waited on.
lf英俊了?
Who said handsome?
相信我
I did.
b於你]有n到停鱿蛭...
Based on the fact that you didn't
meet me in the parking lot,
抱怨有外地人...
hollering about
the two out-of-towners
y行之前在@吃的事
eating here
right before a bank robbery.
他又]fy行
Well, they didn't mention
they was robbing the bank.
他付的F金?
They paid cash?
那也算犯罪?
That a crime now?
他o了多少小M?
How much did they leave?
多少?
How much?
200美元
$200.
他在y行前就o了 所以...
And they left it before
the bank was robbed, so...
在y行前
Uh, before this bank
was robbed.
我要看看他o的X
I'm gonna need
to see them bills.
女士 - 不行
- Ma'am.
- Mm-mm.
女士 他的X是C之一
Ma'am, them bills is evidence.
只有_定他是y行劫犯才算C
Mm-mm, it's evidence
if they're the bank robbers.
在那之前 @是我的小M
Till then, it's my tip.
@可是我房子月供的一半
And half my mortgage.
所以麻┠闳ツ沁拿到C之後
So, you go out there
and you get a warrant,
再磉@Y要走@P
and you come after the money
@PX用肀ＷC我女翰睡大街
that I will be using to keep a roof
over my daughter's head.
有男人了y行 正如她所f的
One man hit the bank,
just like she said.
是的 格子r衫 扣I子
- Yeah.
- Checkered button-down shirt,
牛仔 滑雪面具
jeans, ski mask.
像上都有
- That's all the video will tell us.
- Yep. Yep.
花格r衫 就是他了
Checkered shirt.
That is him.
他在那坐^ o了她200美元小M
They were sitting right over there.
Tipped her $200.
去和N房Y的...
Go wrestle a description
大野U女友vv道理吧
from that big sassy girl
in the kitchen.
你自己]搞定?
You didn't get it yourself?
有 把她那P小M拿到手 我得z查他的X
Oh, and get that tip from her.
We're gonna check them bills.
祝你好\
Good luck.
是啊 我遭到了B抵抗
Yeah, I'd expect some resistance.
哦 有 阿托
Oh, and, Alberto,
打o287的旅^ o咱留g房
call that motel on 287,
get us a room.
我要在@^夜?
We're gonna stay the night?
@可是犯罪F
Well, this is where the action is.
太蠢了
Seems foolish.
怎Nv?
What's that?
靠打劫y行 然後好命花X的好日子...
The days of robbing banks
and trying to live to spend the money...
已一去不头盗
they're long gone.
^κ顷年fv了
Long gone for sure.
Z斯汀L大後想做什N?
What does Justin want to do
when he's grown?
他F在粝榈轮A＆M大W打橄烨
Right now he's dreaming
of slinging a football for A&M.
他和你太像了
He's a lot like you.
我敢肯定@你很眼w - 超乎你的想像
- I bet that puckers your red eye.
- More than you know.
我活了39年 10年在OzY
39 years of life, 10 in jail.
如果他是c我背道而Y 倒是正_的方向
If he turn left where I turned right,
he'll be okay.
*世人皆以吾愚 Let the world call me a fool*
Let the world call me a fool
*唯君平安 Things are right with me and you*
Things are right with me and you
Yaw.
你想要什N?
You want anything?
胡椒博士（一N焦糖碳酸料） zDLights香
Dr Pepper, Winston Lights.
]PS的
It's okay.
Come on.
稚?
What?
看什N看 v人?
What, bitch?
你想找死 混蛋?
You looking for trouble,
motherfucker?
那你Φ胤搅
You came to the right place.
孩子 你不妨假想@Y有十我
Boy, you'd think
there were 10 of me.
哦 是?
Oh, yeah?
你他F在敢@N硬 v人?
Not so fucking tough now,
are you, bitch?
夥 他自找的
Hey, man, he had it coming.
他活 他活
He had it coming.
你存了c血性
You got some spunk left in you.
居然得有
Oh, you remembered the gun.
你已老的_始忘事了
You're getting
to be old hat at this.
那混蛋可能⒘四愕
Asshole could've killed you.
啊 那可未必 老弟
Ah, not the way it would
have gone, little brother.
十我 我警告^你!
10 of me, I told you!
你是想我生?
Are you trying to make me mad?
我f了要胡椒博士 你I的是皮伯先生(可口可樊a品)
I said Dr Pepper.
This is Mr. Pibb.
他只u@
That's all they had.
傻子才喝皮伯先生
Only assholes drink Mr. Pibb.
喝你的吧
Drink up.
你好
Hello.
不!
No!
我不妨...
Now we're talking.
@地方的女人
The women in this place.
你他在f什N?
What the hell you talking about?
我再硪槐 她^就漂亮了
We should get another shot.
They'll be pretty soon enough.
酒保 再o我肀威士忌
Bartender,
whiskeys if you please.
砹
Coming UP-
敬你的孩子
To your boys.
我去Q些Ia
Let's go change that money.
Σ黄 我u了
Sorry.
I just sold my car.
那夥就是@No我X的
This is how the fella paid me.
不管怎NУ腻X 我都收 先生
We take it any way
you bring it, mister.
想玩牌?
Wanna play some poker?
我不博
I don't gamble.
玩牌不的 B你都不
You can't lose at poker,
not even you.
我要喝c酒 去看Aggie(rW院的eQ)比
I'm gonna watch the Aggie game
and have a beer.
你S意
All right, suit yourself.
差不多就行了
Come on, now.
我擦
Suck a D.
e都光了
Don't lose it all.
舔我菊花吧
Eat my A!
死的混蛋
Fucking asshole.
@Y好多Ia啊
That's, uh--
that's quite a stack.
^牌?
Check?
e追我的牌 酋L
Don't chase me, chief.
你是科曼奇族人?
You Comanche?
平原之王
Lords of the Plains.
F在是 o地之王
Lords of Nothing now.
我跟
I call.
亮牌 先生
Show your cards, gentlemen.
你知道科曼奇是什N意思?
Do you know
what Comanche means?
它意味著永h的橙
It means enemies forever.
l是你的橙?
Enemies with who?
每人
Everyone.
你知道那使我成什N?
You know what that makes me?
橙
An enemy.
不
No.
我成科曼奇人
It makes me a Comanche.
他和你L得像?
Does he look like you?
我在他身上能看他的影子
I see his mom in him.
e人f像我
Everybody else sees me.
我也不知道
I don't know.
你有住旅^?
You staying in the hotel?
有
Yeah.
我去你的房g
Take me to your room.
xx你 只是 呃...
Thank you.
Just, uh...
需要女人的嵛K不可u
There's no shame
in needing the touch of a woman.
你需要
You need it.
我知道你很需要
I know you do.
我崦你吧
Just let me touch you.
你是在勾引我弟弟?
Trying to work my little brother?
不 我什N都]做 我… - 坦{ 她什N也]做
- No, I wasn't doing anything, but I...
- Tanner, she didn't do nothin'.
她什N都]做 - 但是 但是 但是 但是 但是
- She didn't do nothin'.
- But, but, but, but, but...
你看到@有一大摞Ia
You saw there was
a stack of chips here.
不要 - 快X是吧?
- Don't.
- Easy mark?
呃 不是 - 那你想怎Nk?
- Uh... no.
- What were you gonna do?
把他У剿的房g 去喊皮l
Bring him up to his room,
call your pimp,
翻倒他 o他下 是不是? - 不  我...
-roll him, drug him, what?
- No. I...
你T用的伎z 是不是? - 坦{ e@
- What were you gonna do?
- Tanner, no.
你介意我先? 真插...
Mind if I sample the goods?
Real fuckin'...
手拿_ 住手 住手
Hands off. Stop it.
Stop it.
你他了! - 打我
- You're fucking crazy!
- Call me.
@有什N麻?
We got a problem here?
一切都很好 - 一切都很好
- It's all good.
只是在酒吧有c喝大了
It's all good.
Just got a little drunk at the bar.
抱歉
Sorry about that.
你他出z後 究竟怎N活^一年的
How the fuck have you managed
to stay out of prison for a year?
一言yM
It's been difficult.
QF金是支票?
Like to pay this out
in cash or check?
留cF金交o黛比
Get some Debbie money.
四成F金 其N支票
Four in cash, rest in check.
您希望用哪家y行的支票?
Who would you like
the check made out to?
德州米德my行
Texas Midlands Bank.
非常xx
Thank you much.
我去找房g住下吧
Let's go get a room.
g迎入住科曼奇66酒店 有As?
Welcome to the Comanche 66.
Do you have a reservation?
]有
We do not.
天 看看你啊
Good Lord, look at you.
如能提供住宿 涌泉相
We would be obliged if you
would provide accommodations,
管我]有As
though we failed to call ahead.
你有麻┝
Boy, you are trouble.
是最糟糕的那N H鄣
I'm the worst kind, darling.
在你B院生命的留之H 你想起我 傻傻的笑
In your last days in the nursing home,
you'll think of me and giggle.
槭颤N上帝? 你槭颤N不回我的祈\?
Why, God?
Why won't you answer my prayers?
你祈求他的椭
You begged him for help,
回首生活 slF一o改
and yet you look around at your life
and nothing is different.
你告戒自己 是上帝指定的@一切
And so you assume
that God has told you no.
然而上帝K]有f不
God doesn't say no.
槭颤N我不能_回R博克市?
Why couldn't we drive back
to Lubbock?
他不在R博克市劫y行
'Cause they ain't robbing banks
in Lubbock.
我不能光看不行 Π?
We're not gonna watch this,
are we?
你不是基督教徒?
Ain't you Christian?
我是 但我不蠢
Yeah, but I ain't stupid.
上帝c@男人的υ K不比上帝c我的狗更多
God doesn't talk through this man
any more than he talks through my dog.
那你好好A你的狗狗
Well, then maybe you should
give your dog a listen.
你不是印第安人?
Ain't you Indian?
你不是身冒火的}人...
You're supposed to be
burning sage
著床舞蹈 l出像s蜜蜂一拥穆音
and dancing around the bed,
whooping like a bee stung you.
我是天主教徒
I'm Catholic.
得了吧
Come on.
得了 我可e著L矛 著火堆跳舞
Come on, I'd rather dance
around the fire with a spear.
你看@目不如用L矛捅我算了
I'd rather have you stab me
with a spear than watch this.
@王八蛋他不懂上帝
This son of a bitch,
he wouldn't know God
除非他能云鹧腿 咬自己的老二
if he crawled up his pant leg
and bit him on the pecker.
他的Q台
Change the damn channel.
F在@才是上帝正在看的
Now, this, this is
what God watches right here.
e心 一就放足球集\
Don't worry, they're gonna have
soccer highlights on soon enough.
因槟阌幸话氲哪西哥血y
That's for your Mexican half.
哇哦 看@孩子
Wow, look at this boy run.
L角牛今年的伍不e啊
Longhorns are gonna have
a good team this year.
足球@N\诱娌荒芾斫
That soccer,
never could understand that.
五q小屁孩能做到的\硬荒芩氵\
Anything a 5-year-old can do
ain't a sport.
ll明的 阿芝特克人?
Who invented it? Aztecs?
把骷t^之的踢硖呷 是吧?
Kickin' around skulls
or something, right?
起砀像科曼奇人的\
Sounds like a Comanche sport.
知道 三Y拜以後
You know, in three weeks,
你就能整天目S便看了
you can watch whatever
you want on TV all day.
或者F在你也可以去你自己房gS便看
Hell, you can do it right now
in your own room.
哦 那有什N纷?
Oh, where's the fun in that?
知道 阿托?
You know what, Alberto?
怎N?
What?
用不了一年
In a year's time,
你就想念我的各N玩笑了
it's my teasing
that you're gonna miss.
你o我上、候我的r候...
It's what you'll laugh about
就X得我的玩笑好笑了
when you stand over my grave
and wish me well.
老天 我真希望那就是明天啊
God, I hope that's tomorrow.
哦 @玩笑M分
Oh, that was a good one.
慢慢你也熟悉玩笑的[T
You'll get the hang of this yet.
天色不早了吧?
Isn't it getting late for you?
是啊
Yeah.
是不早了
Yeah, it is.
噢 老天 老天在上 (前台妹在上)
Oh, heavens above.
天堂在上
Heavens above.
看看@δ套 你他在逗我?
Look at those titties.
Are you fucking kidding me?
质颤N呢?
What are you doing?
睡在T廊 我的未
Sleeping on the porch,
practicing my future.
我@行很危U
It's a dangerous thing
we do for a living.
你很走\...
You're lucky...
已看穿tm
having seen it through
to the end.
我也希望能有那N幸\
I hope I'm that lucky.
哦 其
Oh, well.
]有我跟你搭n 恐怕你距x罪犯太近...
Without me by your side,
I doubt you'll get close enough
早就U境p身了
to a criminal to ever be
in danger again.
我才想δ惚歉呢
Just when I was starting
to feel sorry for you.
印第安人才不εＷ斜歉
Indians ain't supposed
to feel sorry for cowboys.
反^聿
It's the other way around.
你@算z绦腥?
And this makes you the executor?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
不管他怎N起V我 都o法Z走是?
So, no matter what they charge us with,
they can't take it away?
龅馁Y金o法追吧?
There's no way to trace funds
from a casino, all right?
你一旦把支票交oy行  信是o形的
Once you get the checks to the bank,
trust is untouchable.
你跟l都不f一字是吧?
You can't tell
nobody nothing, right?
有什N好f的呢?
Well, what is there to tell?
我的意思是@X你z是博A淼 是吧?
I mean, you boys won
that money gambling, didn't you?
32000美元 付清倒按揭借款
$32,000 pays off
the reverse mortgage.
那些畜生2012年至今都在抽a
And those bastards paid
the property tax from 2012 to now.
~外的11000美元
That's another $11,000.
一共43000美元 就汕辶
So, $43,000
and you are free and clear.
只要再信JTo我髡嬉留置嘟獬C明
Just have the loan officer
fax me a release of lien,
我再D交雪佛的租U管理人
and I'll get that over
to the lease manager at Chevron.
髡嫣a在@名片上 - 好的
- The fax number is on the card.
- Okay.
你诌@文甓嗌馘X?
How much you making
on this deal?
甑牟蛭颐暗娘LU
Not near as much as I'm risking.
那你槭颤N干?
Why you doin' it, then?
你知道 他付o你的借款能少t少
You know, they loaned
the least they could.
只蜃你老F的有基本承Z收益
Just enough to keep your mama poor
on a guaranteed return.
最後只用了25000刀I走她的地皮
Thought they could swipe
her land for $25,000.
太狂了 恨得我牙WW
That's just so arrogant,
it makes my teeth hurt.
看到你z…
To see you boys...
用那托笊自己的Xo自己?
pay those bastards back
with their own money?
如果@不是德州人作L 我都不知道什N是了
Well, if that ain't Texan,
I don't know what is.
多x了
Thank you.
他星期五就取K止抵押品的H回
Now, they can foreclose
on Friday.
你就算赴蹈火
Come hell or high water,
也要在星期四s到柴Y德斯的y行
be at the bank in Childress
on Thursday.
他那群混蛋提早Y束II的
Knowing them fuckers,
they will close early.
及r到_的 - 叫我托比
- We'll be there.
- Oh, and, Toby.
信必由y行
The trust needs to be managed
by a bank.
你真的想要[藏Y金的流向?
You really wanna cover
your tracks?
你得找德州米德m砀氵@信
You get Texas Midland
to handle this trust.
*名人T骨咖啡 II中*
那N 是?
So, what's the plan?
盯著那家y行
We're gonna watch that bank
like a deer feeder.
rgC明我是Φ
In time, we'll be right.
F在我看看都有些什N吃的
Now, let's see
what they got to eat here.
你好 大姐 今天^的怎N?
Howdy, ma'am.
How you doing today?
很 不舒服的
Hot, and I don't mean
the good kind.
好了 你不想要什N?
So, what don't you want?
抱歉?
Pardon?
你不想要什N?
What don't you want?
哦 @ 我看我就呃…
Oh, well, uh,
I think I'll just, uh...
知道 我在@干了44年了
You know, I've been working here
for 44 years.
]有人c^...
Ain't nobody
ever ordered nothing
除了T骨牛排以外的|西
but T-bone steak
and a baked potato.
除了一位募~s淼亩
Except this one asshole
from New York
1987年 那r他想c三文~
tried to order trout
back in 1987.
我家聿毁u特奶奶的三文~
We don't sell
no goddamned trout.
只uT骨牛排
T-bone steaks.
但你可以不要玉米棒子
So, either you don't want
the corn on the cob,
要N不要青豆
or you don't want
the green beans.
所以 你不要什N?
So, what don't you want?
我不要青豆
I don't want green beans.
我也不要青豆
I don't want green beans either.
牛排三分熟
Steaks cooked medium rare.
我的牛排可以的... - 不S多嘴
- Can I get my steak cooked...
- That weren't no question.
好吧
All right.
o你冰茶
Iced tea for you boys.
冰茶不e
Iced tea would be great.
冰茶 xx 大姐
Iced tea, yep.
Thank you, ma'am.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
好吧 我告V你件事
Well, I'll tell you one thing.
]人劫@老太婆
Nobody's gonna rob
this son of a bitch.
相信我
My word.
感X她怎N?
How's she feel?
跑的不e
She runs good.
但A不了什N比吧
Ain't gonna win any races.
A^新墨西哥碟
Got New Mexico plates.
她A^冠?
She got a top?
到底怎N
How she came.
我要她了
We'll take her.
星期五 再蟾媸Ц`
Don't report it stolen till Friday.
雪佛的那夥又p少了租Ufhl款
The guy from Chevron
is dropping off the lease agreement.
你自理]}吧?
Are you okay dealing with that
by yourself?
一人去黛比那Y行?
You okay being with Debbie
by yourself?
住他可不是橙
Remember,
he ain't the enemy.
拿上文件走人 要fxx
Just take the papers,
say thank you.
那油商才是橙 e犯e
The oil man is the enemy,
make no mistake.
他不是我的目
He just ain't ours.
我天黑前就回r
I'll be back to the ranch by dark.
我等你
I will be waiting.
_得像模教 竟後面b了一大堆玩意
Drive like a schoolteacher
with all this shit in the back.
到啤酒rg了吧
Sure feels like beer o'clock.
只管_口
Ask and you shall receive.
*快速取F 往前3英里右D可_*
M
Come in.
死了
Mama died.
什Nr候
When?
Y拜前
A few weeks ago.
好吧 K於[了
Well, good riddance.
o意冒犯
No offense.
你好?
You Okay?
你呢?
You?
@是我欠你的X
Here's the money I owe you.
我以槟u掉牧
I guess you'll be selling
the ranch.
它是孩子的了
It goes to the boys.
是 - 嗯
- Really?
- Mmm.
它算M信里了
It's been put in a trust.
什N意思?
What's that mean?
就是f]有人能u掉它
It means no one can sell it.
@下好了
Great.
我又有新|西得照看了
Something else
I got to take care of.
嗨
Hi.
你弟弟呢?
Where's your brother?
我不知道
I don't know.
也S在朋友家Y吧
Friend's house, I guess.
你怎N不上W?
How come you ain't in school?
]_W
School don't start yet.
F在就是一天纱伍烨
Just two-a-days
for football right now.
你奶奶去世了
Your grandmother died.
我把牧鼋唤o你和你弟弟
I'm giving the ranch
to you and your brother.
得你小r候去^那Y?
Remember going out there
when you was little?
我要拿那牧鲈觞Nk?
What am I supposed to do
with a ranch?
怎佣夹 就是不能u
Anything but sell it.
Y面有石油
We found oil on it.
你和你弟弟拇o需殄X
You and your brother ain't gonna
have to worry about money no more.
F在_始...
Now...
你到很多有P我和...
you may be hearing
a lot of things about me and...
和你叔叔之g的事
your uncle.
不要W我
Don't be like us.
明白?
You hear me?
不管我f了什N 我都不相信的
Whatever I hear,
I won't believe.
不 你得相信
No, you believe it.
一切全是我做的
I did all of it.
你要走不同的人生之路
Now, you, you do it different.
不打算喝?
Ain't gonna drink it?
你我不要像你一 so我啤酒
You tell me not to be like you,
and then you offer me a beer.
到底要怎?
Which is it?
好孩子
Good boy.
孩子好? - 你在质颤N?
- How are the boys?
- What are you doin'?
做些保U措施
Insurance.
我不想上那破玩意
I don't want that shit in the car.
老兄 我下次_奢v
We'll be running two cars
next time, brother.
我上它
They'll ride with me.
所以 @就是你的?
So, this is your plan?
我就@幼在@Y
We're just gonna sit here
z@家分行是不是被他劫
and see if this is the branch
they rob next.
那你又怎幼?
What would you rather do?
你意80英里去W尼...
You wanna drive 80 miles
back to Olney
找那些根本就]有影的指y?
and look for more fingerprints
that we ain't gonna find?
是你想_200英里回R博克市
Or you wanna drive 200 miles
back to Lubbock
去看那些oPo要的部照片 因焊就]有人...
and look at mugshots that don't matter
'cause nobody knows
知道@些王八蛋L什N?
what these sons of bitches
look like?
不然 我就在@等著他@家y行
Or we can just wait here
for them to rob this bank,
而我又十分_定他一定淼
which is the one thing I'm pretty
damn sure they are going to do.
我知道你想致
I know what you're doing.
你在M力拖延rg
You're trying to make this last
as long as you can
拖得rg越L
because the longer it lasts,
你xT廊想的未砭驮竭h
the farther you are
from that front porch.
]有 我在等@些砘锓稿e
No, I'm waitin' for these boys
to make a mistake.
目前]有 但他肯定出岔子
So far they ain't, but they will.
而且就在@家y行
And they're gonna make it here.
所以 放p
So, just relax.
好好享受小的生活吧
Enjoy this little town.
你想住在@Y?
Do you wanna live here?
只有一家古老的五金店
Got an old hardware store
物品售r是家得（美家居Bi店）的杀
that charges twice
what Home Depot does,
有一家餐^ 女招待的皮w堪比尾蛇(的尾h)
one restaurant with
a rattlesnake for a waitress.
我是f @Y的人都怎N生活?
I mean, how is anybody
supposed to make a living here?
@Y住人有150年v史
People have made a living here
for 150 years.
那人在洞穴Y住了十五f年呢
Well, people lived in caves
for 150,000 years,
但你F在不住山洞了啊
but they don't do it no more.
也S你的族人@幼
Well, maybe your people did.
你那拥娜艘
Your people did, too.
很久之前 你的祖先是印第安人...
A long time ago,
your ancestors was the Indians...
直到另外有人硗⑺
till someone came along
and killed them,
把他sM⒔^ 把你同化
broke 'em down,
made you into one of them.
150年前 @Y全都是我祖先的土地
150 years ago, all this
was my ancestors' land.
你F在所看到的一切
Everything you can see.
以及你昨天看到的一切
Everything you saw yesterday.
你的祖Z走了一切
Till the grandparents
of these folks took it.
F在 到他被Z取了
And now, it's been taken
from them.
^e是 不再佑梦淞
Except it ain't no army doing it.
就是那Y的王八蛋(y行家)干的
It's those sons of bitches
right there.
你在想明天的事?
You thinking about tomorrow?
你]想?
Ain't you?
那小酒店的前台妹
The little hotel clerk.
槭颤N那些看起硖鹈赖娜
Why is it always the sweet ones
一旦狂暴起 得那N狂放?
that are such devils
when you get them revved up?
不知道 ]遇甜美型的
Wouldn't know.
Never had a sweet one.
你喜g他狂放 似乎在找人
Yeah, you like them pissed off,
lookin' for someone to blame.
的_是那影
Sure seems that way.
你做的很不e
It's a good thing you're doing.
是我z做的
We're doing it.
明天y行出{T好c
Go easy on the bank teller
tomorrow.
我像年po士那拥厝
I'll be as gentle
as a young nurse.
你?
You coming?
R上
On my Way-
嘿
Hey.
死
Shit.
早上好
Morning.
你想要早餐?
You want some breakfast?
好啊 起聿诲e
Yeah, breakfast sounds good.
我先去茴D分行 再去科曼分行 ?
So we hit the Jayton branch first,
then Coleman, right?
好的 @差不多盗
Yeah, that should get us
what we need.
邮职
Let's do this.
的 死
Ugh... shit.
可他的不是@
That's not part of the fucking plan.
那群混蛋把@家分行oP了
The bastards closed down
the branch.
F在怎Nk 老弟?
What now, little brother?
去科曼分行
Coleman.
你他的在质颤N? - 我得去一趟]局
- What the hell you doing?
- We gotta head to Post.
你他的在质颤N - 得去...
- What the hell are you doing?
- Get...
我得去一趟]局 - 你在f什N?
- We got to head to Post.
- What are you talking about?
我必去一趟]局
We got to head to Post.
我先去科曼
We're going to Coleman.
科曼只有一名出{
There's only one teller in Coleman.
o如何都是不殿~的
Whatever we get won't be enough.
我F在就得去科曼
We go to Coleman right now.
如果那Y不虻脑就去]局
If that ain't enough,
we head to Post.
如果F在不去]局 那就得中午才能到
If we don't leave now for Post,
we won't get there till noon.
你可不想午rgy行吧?
You don't wanna rob a bank
at lunchtime, do you?
我又不知道那地人的T
Yeah, we don't know the patterns
of folks out there.
@NT 都是一拥
The patterns
are the same everywhere.
@些城都僵化了 ]局也是一
All these towns are dead.
Post ain't no different.
那可是家大y行
It's a bigger bank.
我得把你的留在城外
We'll leave your car
just out of town.
快c吧
Come on, now.
操
Shit.
我想我弄懂了
I think I got this figured.
前杉毅y行 都是德州米德my行
First two banks,
they were Texas Midland Banks.
好了 米德my行一共有七家分行
All right, there are seven
branches altogether.
行在沃思堡市
The main branch is in Fort Worth.
他是不去那Y的
They're not gonna mess with that.
他去了W尼分行
All right, they hit
the branch in Olney.
去了阿爻堑哪羌
They hit the one in Archer City.
@Y有一家 - 他未劫
- Then there's the one here.
- Which they did not hit.
阿托 你可以跟著我的思路?
Alberto, will you please
follow me?
]上嘴 e多
Don't let... just keep
your mouth shut
好好著 我要f什N
and just listen
to what I'm gonna say.
@有一家...
There's the one here...
柴德Y斯有一家
then there's the one
in Childress.
茴D有一家
There's the one in Jayton.
@家PT了
That one's closed.
我知道@家PT了!
I know that one's closed!
我知道@家PT了 阿托
I know that one's closed,
Alberto.
我想f的是...
That's my point.
茴D那家PT了
Jayton is closed.
就只剩]局了
That just leaves Post.
他不去搞柴德Y斯的分行
They're not gonna mess
with the bank in Childress.
那子l展很不e
That's a fairly
decent-sized town.
弗r那家不是米德m的 也被他劫了
The branch in Vernon
wasn't Midlands and they hit that.
他其中一去的 就一人
Yeah, one of them did.
Alone.
他一直跑^R路 去那
Then he ran all the way
across the road to get to the car.
他的同夥@然都]有料到l生@件事
I think his partner had no idea
that was gonna happen.
@ξ有什Nr值呢?
What does that mean to us?
@f明他唯一去的地方就是]局
It means that the only branch
that fits the bill is in Post.
那好吧 咱去吧
Well, then let's go.
@地方看起砗芊泵
The town looks busy.
有一c
Little bit.
相信我
My word.
@家太大了
It's too big.
@她f的
That's what she said.
@很不妙
It's no good.
哎 @又不是你的首秀了
Aw, this ain't your first rodeo.
y行越大
Bigger bank...
X越多
more money.
所有人 都他趴到地上!
Everybody,
get on the fucking ground!
他的趴在地上!
Get on the fucking ground!
小姐 他的趴在地上 F在!
Young ladies, get on
the fucking ground! Now!
先生 趴下 趴在地上! 快!
Sir, down!
On the ground! Now!
非常感x你
Thank you very much.
出{T 全w起立!
Tellers, stand up!
把抽洗蜷_!
Open the drawers!
趴好了!
Get down!
o我向後三步!
Take three steps back!
都他把抽辖o我打_ 女士!
Open the fucking drawer,
young lady!
你是@是蠢?
Are you deaf and dumb?
我f你他快o我打_抽!
I said open
the motherfucking drawer!
你趴好了! - 好了 快
- You, down!
- All right. Oh, please.
F在向後退!
Now step back!
很好 *短信：有人正在y行 速*
Very good.
都o我好了
Someone's paying attention.
F在 都他的o我跪下!
Now get on
your motherfucking knees!
嘿
Hey!
趴下!
Stay down!
好了
All right.
兄弟
Dude.
嘿嘿 快走!
Hey, hey, let's go!
快打911
Call 911!
真他日了狗啊
Jesus fucking Christ.
全人都他在朝我_
The whole goddamn town
is shooting at us.
去後 去他的後箱
Get in the back.
Get in the fucking back.
快c 上追!
Come on, let's go!
Get in the car!
e他跑了!
Don't let them get away!
你在後面好 弟弟?
How you doing back there,
little brother?
你他的竟然⑷肆
You fucking killed them.
那些偷偷е砘锏娜...
These concealed carry permits
@然也是劫匪吧?
sure complicate
a bank robbery, don't they?
不是我的e 鬼知道今天是l薪日
It's not my fault it was payday.
@次太出格了 阿坦
This has gone too far, Tan.
本聿有人死的
No one was supposed
to fucking die.
不是他死就是我亡 自己x
It was them or us.
Take your pick.
是的 f吧 格特
Yeah, go, Margaret.
德州米m德]局遭遇劫
Texas Midlands in Post
has just been hit.
我f什N碇?
Ah! What did I tell you?
好
Yeah.
嗯  - 地的警察正在追捕他
- Yeah!
- Locals are in chase.
嫌犯{著一v...
Suspects escaping west
破f的野R向西逃去
in an old Bronco.
明白了 格特 保持j 我正s^去
All right, Margaret, keep us posted.
We're on our way there.
o我一印第安式的嚎叫 戆
Give me an Indian whoop.
Come on.
那些小子要吃T了
These boys are gonna go down.
睃chh然的音
Let's get some giddy-up music
going on there.
不要@曲
Oh, please, not that.
耶
Yeah.
嘿 so^
Hey, hey. Come on.
Snap out of it.
快他o我^
Snap the fuck out of it.
的 o我看看 你中了
Shit, let me see that.
You're hit.
孩子 你被打中了 D^去
Boy, you're hit.
Get the back.
你活下淼 百分百]}
Well, you'll live.
It's a through and through.
壕o口 然後包好 必oo包住
Compress it. Wrap it up.
You got to wrap it up tight.
前後都要包 前後
Front and back,
front and back.
包oc
Wrap it tight.
噢 兄弟 F在o我J真好了
Oh, brother, hear me now,
hear me clear.
如果你不想成槟愫⒆由命中的污c
Unless you wanna be a black mark
on your sons' lives,
拿出c美洲{精神
I need you mountain lion mean.
到了?
You hear me?
到了
I hear you.
美洲{精神 -
- Mountain lion mean.
- Yeah.
]事的 一切都好的
Yeah. It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
猿肿
- Hold on.
- Yeah.
快走
Go.
o 把X拿著
Here, take the money.
咱走 - 去瞿
- Let's go.
- Get to the casino.
按洗X
Change the money
like we planned.
@是你的 @_有效
This was your plan,
and it worked.
每一步都是
Every step of the way.
相信自己
Trust it.
你淙ツ?
Where are you headed?
e傻了
Don't be stupid.
我勰 托比
I love you, Toby.
我J真的
I mean it.
我也勰
I love you, too.
嘿 托比 去你的
Hey, Tobe, go fuck yourself.
去你的
Go fuck yourself.
*光N的早晨我信步而行*
As I walked out
one sunny morning
*一眼瞅牛仔哥~著大步*
I spied a young cowboy
a loping along
*他的帽子煸诒翅*
His hat was laid back
*他的R刺叮叮的*
His spurs were a jinglin'
*他走近我的r候 唱著@首歌*
And as he come near me
He's singing this song
*咿辟咳咿吼 你@小狗狗*
Yippee hiyiyo.
You little doggies.
*@是你的不幸 而不是我的*
It's your misfortune
and none of my own
@就是所^白人的直X
This is what they call
white man's intuition.
也叫瞎抓到死老鼠
Sometimes a blind pig
finds a truffle.
*@是你的不幸 而不是我的*
It's your misfortune
and none of my own
快後退 噢 靠!
Back up! Oh, shit!
快 快 快走!
Go! Move!
相信我
My word.
好吧 看砦需要一支特警
All right, We're gonna need
a SWAT unit up here
和一架直升wC 碜ツ砘锪
and a helo to pin
these boys down.
嫌犯是一名白人男性
Suspect is a white male.
所有人散_
Guys, spread it out!
Ψ匠钟械 腰!
He's got a rifle.
Get down!
Ψ匠钟械 腰!
He's on the ridge!
我看他了!
Come on, I see him!
只有一人?
There's just one?
是的 只有一人
Yep, just one.
本硎怯人的
There's supposed
to be two of them.
也S在上就抓住了一
Maybe the town folks got one.
那N抓住的那 肯定是明出主意的人
Well, if they did,
they got the smart one.
@老小子直了
This old boy
is out of his mind.
你不如翻越{谷 用斧u@混蛋?
Why don't you slip up this canyon
and tomahawk that son of a bitch?
巡警奚 求支援
Ranger down.
Call it in.
快倒 後退 @些皮卡都後退!
Get back! Back!
Back those trucks up!
後退!
Get back!
那些卡都後退
Get these trucks back.
快後退!
Back up!
他後退
Back them up.
你熟悉@的地形?
How well do you know the land
around here?
t如指掌
Like the back of my hand.
那好 他就藏在那山脊惭Y
All right, he's hid up
in that brush on that hill.
能我@到他後面去?
Can you get me up there
behind him?
o我30分 可以拿下那混蛋
Give me a half hour,
I'll have that bastard
後面的地形正好能o我的做掩o
field dressed on the hood
of my truck.
你]必要@N做 只管我^去
I can't let you do that.
You just get me there.
如果真像你f的那 那可足足500ah
That's gonna be a 500-yard shot
if he's where you said.
只管我^去!
Just get me there!
操
Shit.
你好?
How are you doing?
好 你呢?
Good. You?
你淙ツ耗?
Where are you headed?
伊多索
Ruidoso.
你哪淼?
Where you from?
哈姆林
Hamlin.
x@N荒龅穆肪?
Taking the scenic route?
x了l唯一能走的路而已
Taking the only way I can.
他封了]局的路
They got the road closed
at Post.
每一l下口都被封了
Everywhere you turn
they got the road closed.
я{照了? - 是的 我Я
- You got your license on you?
- Yes, I do.
在@稍等一下
Wait right there.
好的 L官
Yes, sir.
先生 - 嗯
- Sir.
- Yeah.
一路L
Have a good day.
多x
Thanks much.
你有c喘不上獍
You're pretty winded.
你我黹_ 鬼了 @可是我的
You oughta let me take the shot.
Hell, it's my gun.
F在不是了
Not on your life.
他是我的
He's mine.
就在涞淖筮
Just left of the tree.
我砀愣ㄋ
I got him.
我看到你了
I got you.
平原之王
Lord of the Plains.
就是我
That's me.
德州高速路巡和地警察
Texas Highway Patrol
and the locals
在我身後的山上追s匪
chased the robbers
to this hillside behind me,
子西的20里外 交火依然在^m
20 miles west of town,
where the gunfight continued.
F在我得知
And right now we do know
巡警察R焖埂h密D借用地居民的一把砀
Ranger Marcus Hamilton
killed one of the gunmen
懒似渲幸持嫌犯
using a rifle he actually borrowed
from a resident here.
我F在不清楚@嫌犯的名字
We don't know the name
of that suspect yet...
真走\
Lucky guy-
rg卡得好
Just in the nick of time, too.
@N概率不太有
What are the odds?
好吧 F在@PX
Now, this, uh, satisfies
正好能清倒按揭借款和...
both the reverse mortgage loan
and the, uh...
我替你母H代付的款
and the back taxes that we've paid
on your mother's behalf.
然 我@N做是出於好心
We do that as courtesy,
of course.
把留置嘟獬C明髡娼o@a
You can fax the release of lien
to that number.
一律?
An attorney?
好的 嗯 我把|西髡姘l^去...
All right, well, I'll... I'll get that
faxed over to your attorney
在@L末之前
by the end of the week.
F在就是L末 我要H眼看著你做
It is the end of the week.
I wanna watch you do it.
@需要crg
Well, it takes a little time
to prepare.
我一天都有空
I got all day.
有了
Here we go.
好的 就@
Okay. That's it.
很s幸c你接洽
And it's been a pleasure
doing business with you.
你}
Let me ask you a question.
你有信I?
Do y'all manage trusts?
嘿 R焖 你不是退休了?
Hey, Marcus,
ain't you supposed to be retired?
你好
Howdy.
雪莉 - 很高d看你
- Shelley.
- Nice to see you.
你好 R焖 - 嘿 格特
- Well, hey, Marcus.
- Hey, Margaret.
一子老百姓的滋味怎N?
Been awhile.
How's life as a civilian?
就 你知道的...
Oh, just, you know...
我可以看一下霍A德的n案?
Think I can take a peek
at Mr. Howard's file?
坦{・霍A德
Tanner Howard.
行了 我]有更好的差事可
Oh, come on.
I ain't got nothing better to do.
在我的桌子上
It's at my desk.
呃
Uh...
他在一次狩C事故中 ⒘怂父H是吧?
Killed his father
in a hunting accident, huh?
我倒是想知道四月份的Y}里 有什N可以狩C的
I'd love to know what he was hunting
in the barn in April.
因乐害罪 被P押在亨茨S十年
10 years in Huntsville
for aggravated assault.
他的z友於2012年被放
Cellmate was released in 2012.
@刑7年 他因劫大斯普林市y行...
Before that,
he served seven years
被提起公V
on bank robbery charges
up in Big Spring.
一直D追捕其z友 但至今仍是未果
Been trying to track him down,
but no luck so far.
你都忽略了他的兄弟?
You all are off the brother?
他和@些劫案毫oPS
There's nothing that links him
to the robberies.
那弗r市的小服T又怎N解?
Now, what about
that little waitress in Vernon?
我o她看了照片
Yeah, we showed her photos.
她f不JR他
She said she didn't
recognize him.
而且你拿走她的小M 令她O其沮
Pretty upset you took
her tips as evidence.
她^υ诟闶
She sure was sassy.
你把照片o那位老油子看了?
You show that
to that old timer?
看了 他f他不像是那用餐的小伙
Yep. He said he didn't look
like the fella from the diner.
他也]J出坦{
He didn't recognize
Tanner's photo either.
想法庭判令{查他的y行~艉娃r
Yeah, tried to get a court order
on his bank accounts and the ranch,
地z官才不做@事
DA wouldn't do it.
托比案底清白 ]有任何犯罪
Toby's got no record.
He's never been arrested.
唯一出庭是x婚案
His only court appearance
was at his divorce.
他K不符合案情 R焖
He don't fit the bill, Marcus.
人不是一出生就劫的
People don't start out
robbing banks.
是要慢慢升的 比如他的混蛋哥哥
They graduate to it
like his asshole brother.
再f 我到那的r候
Besides,
when we was out there,
看山M雪佛的T工
we saw two crews from Chevron
一Mw井帽 一M安b石油井
capping wells
and putting in pumpjacks.
F龉こf@Y...
Engineers out there
said they're gonna pull
每月a出2000桶原油
2,000 barrels a month
off that place.
你X得法官o你授...
You just try convincing a judge
to issue warrants on somebody
以劫管理信的y行四f美元槊立案
set to clear $50,000 a month
而那人s每月Q入5f美元
for robbing $40,000 from the bank
that manages the family trust.
米德m管理信I?
Midland manages the trust?
你J殂y行是想查水落石出
You'd think they'd want
this thing figured out.
我X得y行什N都不在乎
I don't think the bank cares
about anything
除了S持信的正常\行
but keeping that trust
right where it is.
死 y行方面比托比的律不肯配合
Hell, they were less cooperative
than Toby's attorney.
R焖 他不是嫌疑犯 你也已退休了
Marcus, he's not a suspect
and you are retired.
哦 你的
Oh, I hear you.
你喜g@桌子?
You like my desk?
至少不
I don't hate it.
嘿 回^ R焖
Hey, I'll see you, Marcus.
知道我是l?
Know who I am?
我是⒘四愀绺绲娜
I'm the man
who killed your brother.
我知道
I know.
我知道你已退休 你@算擅J
I also know you're retired
and you're trespassing.
哦 你F在就可以懒宋 你的嗬
Well, you could shoot me now
and be within your rights.
你手扣在扳C上 多方便
You toting a gun and all,
how convenient.
我猜你也有一支
I figure you got one, too.
介意我坐?
Mind if I sit?
M戆
Go ahead.
啤酒?
You want a beer?
可以 我再也不用糖诹
Sure.
I ain't on duty no more.
x了
Thanks.
在@坐著吹著小L真芤
It's nice out here
in this breeze, huh,
管F在已降亓
now that it's cooled down.
你怎N做到的?
How did you do it?
算我]f
Oh, never mind.
哦 ]PS 我及r搞清楚的
I'll figure that out in time.
槭颤N?槭颤N要帜鞘?
Why?
Why did you do it?
我可以理解你哥哥坦{的C
I know why your brother,
Tanner, did it.
他y行是因樗喜g
He robbed them banks
because he liked it.
他在300a外射死了我的同事 就因樗喜g
He shot my partner 300 yards away
'cause he liked it.
...X得爽
It made him feel good.
如果不是我一射爆他的X{
If I hadn't blown
his shit for brains out,
@T口有另外一v湫碌钠た K外焖上摩托
there'd be a new truck out front
with jet skis
或者他想I啥就I啥
or whatever else
he could think to buy.
他花光所有X 好o他藉口再去偷
He'd spend it all just to give
an excuse to steal some more.
但你不@
But not you.
]o@YI什N新|西...
There's nothing new
around here...
除了井
except them pumpjacks.
@些C器砘锩月...
Each one of them
making you a month
o你的X大大超^你兄弟zB四家y行的和
what you and your brother stole
from all four banks combined.
那N臀蚁胂
Help me understand, then.
臀蚁朊靼锥加兴人G了性命...
Help me understand
why four people died...
似乎你淼腻X K]有花掉
so you could steal money
that it don't seem you've spent,
感X@XK不是急需的
that it don't seem you need.
你有家人?
You got a family?
我搭n 一大家子人
My partner had a family.
A big one.
他家後院可]有石油井
They don't got no pumpjacks
in their backyard.
我]⒛愕呐笥 - 不 你⒘
- I didn't kill your friend.
- Yes, you did.
你幕後策的一切
By setting this thing
in motion.
你X得我相信是你X抽的哥哥策的一切?
You expect me to believe
your dimwitted brother planned this?
才不 策很明
Oh, no.
This was smart.
明的是你
This was you.
我F了一子
I've been poor my whole life.
我父母F 祖父母也F
So were my parents,
their parents before them.
F就像z鞑...
It's like a disease...
一代又一代地飨氯 成B疾
passing from generation to generation,
becomes a sickness.
就是@
That's what it is.
魅窘o你JR的每一人...
Infects every person you know...
但我鹤硬荒茉俑F下去了
but not my boys.
不可以
Not anymore.
F在@凫端
This is theirs now.
我一生]⑦^人
Now, I ain't never killed
no one in my life,
但如果你想我哪汩_刀 老人家
but if you want me to start with you,
let's get on with it, old man.
看看你抽出手之前 我能否一Z翻你
See if you can grab that pistol
before I blast you off this porch.
你好 - 怎N回事?
- Howdy.
- What's going on?
家i回家了啊
The hogs are back
in the garden.
野i_道 游疵
Feral hogs tearing up this place
something fierce.
@是哪位?
Who's this?
我是你丈夫的一老朋友
I'm an old friend
of your husband.
是前夫
Ex-husband.
我只是硌b修房子的
I'm just working on the house.
哦 你不住在@Y?
Oh, you don't live here?
不 @Y不凫段 是他的房a
No, it's not mine.
It's theirs.
哦
Oh.
造福後代的事情
The things we do
for our kids, huh?
那N
Well...
我最好走了
I best be going.
女士
Ma'am.
我也走了 黛比 我要去洗洗乾Q
Me, too, Debbie.
I'm gonna wash up,
大概明天9c回硗瓿汕伴T的活
be back around 9:00 tomorrow
to finish the front.
然後浞鬯⑵漯N部分
Start painting the extension
等m迪放W回家後
and then help Randy
with his homework
和他完成作I 好?
when he gets back
from school, okay?
好的
Okay-
嘿
Hey.
我在上租了一g小屋
I rent a little house in town.
如果你想找我^m@
If you wanna stop by
and finish this conversation,
Srg迎
you're welcome anytime.
哦 我的
Oh, I'd like that.
回^了
I'll be seeing you.
是啊 很快 我想
Yeah.
Soon, I hope.
我浜昧私Y@一切了
I'm ready to be done
with this.
你永h都不了Y o是什N
You'll never be done with it
no matter what.
它伴S你K身 孩子
It's gonna haunt you, son,
for the rest of your days.
但你不孤
But you won't be alone.
它也伴S我K身
It's gonna haunt me, too.
如你有空拜L 也S我o你安
If you stop by,
maybe I'll give you peace.
也S吧 也S是我o你安
Maybe.
Maybe I'll give it to you.